Lovesick Girls
영원한 밤
창문 없는 방에 우릴 가둔 love
What can we say
매번 아파도 외치는 Love
다치고 망가져도 나
뭘 믿고 버티는 거야
어차피 떠나면 상처투성인 채로
미워하게 될 걸
끝장을 보기 전 끝낼 순 없어
이 아픔을 기다린 것처럼
아마 다 잠깐일지도 몰라
우린 무얼 찾아서 헤매는 걸까
But I don't care
I'll do it over and over
내 세상 속에 너만 있으면 돼
We are the lovesick girls
네 멋대로 내 사랑을 끝낼 순 없어
이 아픔 없인 난 아무 의미가 없어
But we were born to be alone
Yeah we were born to be alone
But why we still looking for love
No love letters, no X and O's
No love, never, my exes know
No diamond rings that set in stone
To the left, better left alone
Didn't wanna be a princess
I'm priceless
A prince not even on my list
Love is a drug that I quit
No doctor could help when I'm lovesick
아마 다 잠깐일지도 몰라
우린 무얼 찾아서 헤매는 걸까
불안한 내 눈빛 속에 널 담아
아프더라도 너만 있으면 돼
We are the lovesick girls
네 멋대로 내 사랑을 끝낼 순 없어
이 아픔 없인 난 아무 의미가 없어
But we were born to be alone
Yeah we were born to be alone
But why we still looking for love
사랑은 slippin' and fallin',
사랑은 killing your darling
아프다 아물면 또 찾아오는 이 겁 없는 떨림
들리지 않아 what you say
이 아픔이 난 행복해
나를 불쌍해하는 네가 내 눈엔 더 불쌍해
We are the lovesick girls
네 멋대로 내 사랑을 끝낼 순 없어
이 아픔 없인 난 아무 의미가 없어
We are the lovesick girls
모두 결국 떠나가고
Lovesick girls
내 눈물이 무뎌져도
아프고 또 아파도
But we're still looking for love